newsiosity.com 2016-05-10

# Privacy Policy

At Newsiosity.com we understand the importance of protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information collected when anyone is on our site or uses the services we provide; it neither addresses nor applies to individuals or third party practices over which we have no control. This includes but is not limited to cookies which may be used by our advertisers.

Newsiosity.com only collects information pertinent to our website; as such, our stated goal is to customize your experience and let you get the most out of what we offer. To that end:

  * Newsiosity.com will never rent, share or sell any of the personal information you provide.
  * For your security and privacy, your information is protected with a password created by you.
  * You will always have access to your personal information and you may edit or delete it at any time.
  * In an effort to protect children, users must be 13 years old to use our Support Groups and 18 years old to use the Online Counseling services..

### At Newsiosity.com, information is collected in two ways:

  1. By what you provide to us when you enter your registration information, which requires an email address as well as some basic information about you. You do not need to register to use our site, and if you do register you may omit certain information; however, please be aware that doing so may restrict you from enjoying the full range of our web site. If you choose to create a profile with a Sign-In Name, Bio, Recent Posts etc., Newsiosity.com makes it possible for other users to browse the site for this information.
  2. By what your computer automatically provides to us. Via our server, Newsiosity.com collects your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit in an effort to help us administer and improve our site. Our servers use cookies to enable us to recognize your computer and facilitate use of our site. They do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information gathered by cookies with any personal information provided by you through registration. You may disable cookies from the "help" toolbar on your internet browser.

### Changes & Conditions of Use

Changes or amendments to our Privacy Policy may occur now and again as warranted. However, information is always and only subject to the policy in place at the time it is collected. Should we feel the need to execute a change in the Policy, we will announce the change on our website so that our users are made aware of the change and may act accordingly.

Finally, the conditions of use (visits to our website, including the information collected, our use of that information, and any future disputes regarding issues of privacy) are subject to both this Policy and our [Terms of Use](http://www.newsiosity.com/terms-conditions).
